[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie The Phantom of the Opera, what does Christine do to the Phantom before leaving with Raoul for the first time?", "correct_answer": "She kisses him.", "incorrect_answers": ["She puts his mask back on.", "She sings for him.", "She hugs him."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the Weird Al Yankovic movie UHF, what hand did Uncle Harvey win the TV station with?", "correct_answer": "One pair of 7s", "incorrect_answers": ["Full house", "Two pair, aces high", "One pair of 9s"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "El Dorado stars actors such as James Caan, Robert Mitchum and John Wayne. Shooting of the movie started in late 1965 with the release following in this year.", "correct_answer": "1967", "incorrect_answers": ["1966", "1965", "1975"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Hollywood actress portrayed Dorothy in the 1939 film The Wizard of Oz?", "correct_answer": "Judy Garland", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "Marlene Dietrich", "Ginger Rogers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "High consumption of meat protein deprives the body of calcium.  Lack of calcium causes this disease.", "correct_answer": "Osteoporosis", "incorrect_answers": ["Nausea", "Obesity", "Cholera"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which verb is defined as \u201cto put forward a suitable person to incur the mudgobbling and deadcatting of the opposition\u201d in Ambrose Bierce\u2019s satirical book The Devils Dictionary", "correct_answer": "Nominate", "incorrect_answers": ["Fire", "Promote", "Recommend"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which year was Albert Einstein born?", "correct_answer": "1879", "incorrect_answers": ["1869", "1899", "1889"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1981 Jane starred in this movie with her father Henry Fonda.", "correct_answer": "On Golden Pond", "incorrect_answers": ["The China Syndrome", "Barbarella", "Wall Street"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This plant, which is native to Venezuela and northern Brazil, is named after a tribe. It is used for producing drinks with energizing and stimulating effect.", "correct_answer": "Guarana", "incorrect_answers": ["Mango", "Papaya", "Guava"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In The World Is Not Enough, while skiing, 007 and Elektra are chased by what kind of vehicles at the pipelines end?", "correct_answer": "Parahawk helicopters", "incorrect_answers": ["Armed sleds", "Cessna airplanes", "Snowmobiles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "From what two people did Andie get the two dresses to make her prom dress in the movie Pretty in Pink?", "correct_answer": "Her father and Iona", "incorrect_answers": ["Her father and Blane", "Duckie and Iona", "Blane and Iona"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The blue whale is the largest animal, but what is the largest toothed whale on the planet?", "correct_answer": "Sperm whale", "incorrect_answers": ["Cuviers Beaked Whale", "Orca", "All of these"]}]